<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Civitas</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome_user">Welcome, %1$s!</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must have at least 8 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home Page</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="home_fragment_label">Your home</string>
    <string name="profile_fragment_label">Your profile</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="work_in_progress">Work in progress...</string>
    <string name="view_profile">View profile</string>
    <string name="shared_preferences_name" translatable="false">pt.unl.fct.civitas.sharedPreferences</string>
    <string name="shared_preferences_token" translatable="false">pt.unl.fct.civitas.authToken</string>
    <string name="prompt_confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="prompt_name">Name</string>
    <string name="action_register">Register</string>
    <string name="prompt_email" translatable="false">E-mail</string>
    <string name="profile_visibility_undefined" translatable="false">UNDEFINED</string>
    <string name="profile_visibility_public" translatable="false">PUBLIC</string>
    <string name="profile_visibility_private" translatable="false">PRIVATE</string>
    <string name="prompt_profile_visibility">Profile visibility</string>
    <string name="register_failed">Register failed</string>
    <string name="action_register_long">Don\'t have an account? Create one here</string>
    <string name="register_success">User successfully registered. Welcome to our community!</string>
    <string name="error_different_passwords">The passwords don\'t match</string>
    <string name="prompt_telephone">Home phone (optional)</string>
    <string name="prompt_mobilePhone">Mobile phone (optional)</string>
    <string name="prompt_nif">NIF</string>
    <string name="invalid_email">Not a valid email address</string>
    <string name="invalid_name">Not a valid name</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="sign_out_success">Successfully signed out</string>
    <string name="error_show_profile">Error retrieving profile data</string>
    <string name="prompt_telephone_short">Home phone</string>
    <string name="prompt_mobilePhone_short">Mobile phone</string>
    <string name="prompt_nif_short">NIF (can\'t be changed)</string>
    <string name="apply_changes">Apply changes</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="terrains">Terrains</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="terrain_fragment_label">Your terrains</string>
    <string name="error_show_terrains">Error retrieving terrain data</string>
    <string name="zero_terrains">No terrains found for this user</string>
    <string name="invalid_nif">Not a valid NIF</string>
    <string name="error_edit_profile">Error changing profile data</string>
    <string name="add_terrain">Add terrain</string>
    <string name="edit_terrain">Edit terrain</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="set_terrain_area">Set terrain area</string>
    <string name="parish_amendoa" translatable="false">Amêndoa</string>
    <string name="parish_cardigos" translatable="false">Cardigos</string>
    <string name="parish_carvoeiro" translatable="false">Carvoeiro</string>
    <string name="parish_envendos" translatable="false">Envendos</string>
    <string name="parish_ortiga" translatable="false">Ortiga</string>
    <string name="parish_macao_penhascoso_aboboreira" translatable="false">Mação, Penhasco e Aboboreira</string>
    <string name="terrain_data_insert_prompt">Please tell us about your terrain</string>
    <string name="terrain_name_prompt">Name of this terrain</string>
    <string name="parish">Parish</string>
    <string name="article">Article (mandatory)</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="current_usage">Current usage</string>
    <string name="previous_usage">Previous usage</string>
    <string name="owners_long">Other owners (format: \"user1\" or \"user1,user2,user3\")</string>
    <string name="section">Section (mandatory)</string>
    <string name="terrain_coverage_type">Type of terrain coverage</string>
    <string name="terrain_documentation">Terrain documentation</string>
    <string name="upload_file">Upload file</string>
    <string name="changes_success">Changes successful</string>
    <string name="terrain_info_fragment_label">New terrain</string>
    <string name="invalid_article">Invalid article</string>
    <string name="invalid_section">Invalid section</string>
    <string name="help_add_terrain">Tap the map to create a point. Tap finish once you\'ve added all necessary points to form your terrain.</string>
    <string name="error_terrain_intersection">Conflict with already approved terrains detected.</string>
    <string name="prompt_name_terrain">Name (you can\'t have two terrains with the same name)</string>
    <string name="terrain_list">Terrains</string>
    <string name="article_uneditable">Article (cannot be changed)</string>
    <string name="section_uneditable">Section (cannot be changed)</string>
    <string name="terrain_id_uneditable">Terrain ID (cannot be changed)</string>
    <string name="terrain_area">Total area of this terrain</string>
    <string name="hectares" translatable="false">hectares</string>
    <string name="other_owners">Other owners</string>
    <string name="owners_add">Add other owners (ex. \"user2,user3\")</string>
    <string name="your_terrain">Your terrain</string>
    <string name="terrain_get_directions">Get directions</string>
    <string name="terrain_share_self">You can\'t share a terrain with yourself</string>
    <string name="error_terrain_update">Updating terrain info has failed...</string>
    <string name="error_terrain_share">Sharing of the terrain has failed... please re-check the additional owner field</string>
    <string name="owners">Owners</string>
    <string name="terrain_added">Terrain saved</string>
    <string name="success_terrain_share">Terrain sharing successful</string>
    <string name="terrain_add_owners">Add owners</string>
    <string name="error_add_terrain">Error adding terrain... the inserted data is likely the cause</string>
    <string name="success_add_terrain">Terrain registered successfully!</string>
    <string name="terrain_id">Terrain ID</string>
    <string name="shared_preferences_pfp" translatable="false">pt.unl.fct.civitas.profilePic</string>
    <string name="error_server_code">"Server error: code "</string>
    <string name="error_token_expired">Your session has expired. Please login again.</string>
    <string name="large_text" translatable="false">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="help_fragment_label">Help</string>
    <string name="help_page_text">
        "Civitas é uma aplicação de gestão de terrenos, desenhada para ser usada em conjunto com o nosso site web.\n\n"
        "Quando regista um terreno na aplicação, este irá ficar guardado, para quando tiver a documentação necessária "
        "para o seu registo oficial, possa submeter no nosso site web. Ao fazer isto, apenas terá de esperar "
        "até o seu terreno ser aprovado, e é tudo!\n\n"

        "Após entrar na sua conta, pode ver os seus terrenos já registados no separador \"Terrenos\".\n"
        "Poderão aparecer em várias cores diferentes, com os seguintes significados:\n\n"

        "Roxo - terreno guardado mas ainda não submetido o registo oficialmente\n"
        "Amarelo - à espera de aprovação; apenas após registo da documentação necessária\n"
        "Verde - terreno aprovado!\n"
        "Vermelho - terreno rejeitado… tente corrigir informação ou adicionar com nova área\n\n"

        "Na página dos terrenos, poderá começar a registar o seu terreno pressionando simplesmente um botão. "
        "Insira a informação necessária e relevante, e quando terminar, pode avançar para indicar "
        "a área do terreno o melhor que conseguir.\n"
        "Para desenhar esta área, pressione no mapa para criar pontos um a um, e tem um terreno pronto a registar! "
        "Enquanto estiver a desenhar a área do seu terreno, vai poder ver no mapa os terrenos já aprovados "
        "de outros utilizadores. Não convém passar por cima...\n\n"

        "Além de ver os seus terrenos e adicionar novos, pode consultar a lista dos seus terrenos "
        "no canto superior esquerdo, e pressionar os seus nomes para os localizar no mapa.\n"
        "No canto superior direito, pode pressionar para se localizar a si mesmo no mapa, caso nos permita. "
        "E finalmente, pode pressionar um dos seus terrenos para: consultar as suas informações, "
        "alterar algumas delas, obter direções para o terreno, ou até indicar outros proprietários!\n"
        "Para indicar outros proprietários, apenas introduza os seus nomes de utilizador no campo "
        "dos novos proprietários, no formato indicado, e pressione \"Partilhar terreno\".\n\n"

        "Esperamos que contribua para o menor abandono destas terras!\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="hyperlink"><a href="https://civitasadc.appspot.com">https://civitasadc.appspot.com</a></string>
    <string name="add_vertex_location">Add point at your location</string>
    <string name="name_mandatory">Name (mandatory)</string>
</resources>